Betty in Search of a Thrill is a comedy, drama
film directed by Phillips Smalley.
After graduating from a convent school, Betty travels to New
York to visit her relatives, the Hastings.
She quickly catches the eye of Jim Denning, a wealthy neighbor who proposes to her, but Betty
decides to experience city life before settling down and finds work as a salesclerk.
When the floorwalker becomes too familiar, Betty quits and her showgirl friend Maizie Follette helps her get a job as a
cabaret dancer, but Betty finds that’s a tough racket too and decides city life on the loose isn’t for her.
Betty, played by Elsie Janis.
Jim Denning, played by Owen Moore.
June Hastings, played by Juanita Hansen.
Mr. Hastings, played by Herbert Standing.
Mrs. Hastings, played by Vera Lewis.
A Boarder, played by Harry Ham.
Betty in Search of a Thrill is a lost 1915 American silent adventure film that was
directed by Phillips Smalley and Lois Weber and written by Elsie Janis.
The film stars Elsie Janis, Owen Moore, Juanita Hansen,
Herbert Standing, Vera Lewis, and Harry Ham.
The film was released on May 17, 1915, by Paramount Pictures.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.